QIHUANG CLINIC
SIZHUKONG, ERMEN
That person also told me
that in the afternoon of June 30th,
those two people would head
to Qihuang Clinic.
He told me to wait for them there.
-A clinic?
-An unlicensed qigong center.
It's probably sealed.
What about the photo?
I burned it.
It's a rule in the gang.
What does "make them disappear" mean?
Kill them?
I don't know either.
He picked up the phone call and vanished.
Officer He.
I never intended to kill anyone.
I just wanted to scare them,
so they would leave Weiyang
and never come back again.
That's disappearing, isn't it?
I waited and waited, but no one ever came.
So, I went out to take a peek.
Then, I heard screams on the floor above.
I then realized that the woman
and the old man
didn't head to the 17th floor,
but the 18th floor.
I went to Pattia before.
I know there is a secret door there.
I figured they might
be hiding on the rooftop.
But I walked around and didn't see them.
Who gave you the keys?
I used some tricks.
Then, I wanted to get out of there.
Then you people came to the 18th floor,
group by group.
I couldn't run away.
I waited until the sun set.
I couldn't stand it anymore.
So, I let it out.
I was all sweaty and dirty,
and I thought
I couldn't just suffer this for nothing.
I must get the balance of the payment.
I must show the gang how good I am.
So, I bluffed.
I grabbed a bag,
made myself a bloody cloak,
and told everyone
that I had killed two people.
Then, the blood in the bag…
It's all chicken blood.
Test it if you don't trust me.
If it's human blood,
just shoot me on the spot.
What were you doing in 407?
Who gave you the job?
I don't know who he is.
-How much did he offer?
-Forty-thousand yuan.
But he still owes me
the balance of 30,000 yuan.
You can't even recognize him.
How are you supposed to ask him to pay?
He said he'd call me after the job.
Buddy.
You killed them.
Why would he contact you?
So that you can turn yourself in
to the police?
Gosh.
Did anyone see you when you did it?
Answer me!
I think
I saw someone when I was leaving.
You think?
Idiot! And you can sleep
at night like this?
Find that witness and silence him.
That old man in 407 saw me.
I had to silence him.
Someone still owes me 30,000 yuan.
If someone tells the police,
I will be busted.
I was very polite to him.
Yes.
He was quite polite.
But really, I've never seen him before.
Never.
Last night,
I was reading a detective novel in my bed.
I was captivated by it, and it kept me up.
I couldn't sleep,
so I thought I could climb some stairs
and sweat a little before I went to bed.
As soon as I opened
the door to the staircase,
I felt so drowsy.
My eyelids were heavy.
I could barely keep them open.
So, I went back to sleep.
I didn't see anything.
I didn't see him.
You love to read detective novels?
Yes.
You too?
We have the same hobby.
What kind of detective novels?
The classical European ones or--
Du Mandun.
If you didn't see Jin Manlang,
why did you call the police?
I'm a fan of mysteries.
Did you notice?
Yesterday, someone disappeared
in a locked room on the 18th floor.
Today, everyone is singing
that nursery song.
Isn't that just like the prelude
to a murder in every detective novel?
Speak plainly, please.
Continue. I understand everything.
-Okay. Listen.
-Sure.
I thought the whole thing
could never be this simple.
-At first…
-You didn't even see a shadow.
Who says I didn't see anything?
I saw her clearly.
I saw the woman twice.
I saw her carrying… Like…
Relax. Tell us one by one.
I first saw her
in the morning several days ago.
Right at the corner of the staircase.
The second time I saw her was yesterday.
I was playing gateball
at the park with Meng and Wang.
I saw the woman walking by
while carrying an old man.
She looked exactly like the woman
I had met on the staircase
several days ago.
Are you sure they were identical?
Try to recall.
Did anything stand out
when you saw the woman?
-Anything that stood out?
-Yes.
She had medical patches on her wrists.
Over here and over here.
These are probably marks
left by medical patches.
It matches.
How so?
The medical patch has her name on it?
This is an important lead.
What kind of woman would use
medical patches on her wrists?
It must have something to do with her job.
That's just your opinion.
I think she might have injured
her wrists while she carried things.
Or she might have a scar
that she didn't want anyone to see.
The possibilities are endless.
Yes. You're absolutely right.
All these possibilities
are possible clues to this murder.
Must you get us a murder case?
Someone has hired a man to kill them.
How is this not a murder?
Officer, is this truly a murder?
We analyzed the blood
in the bag and on the rooftop.
It's not human blood.
The saliva sample from the cigarette butt
matches Jin Manlang.
It seems like someone
has tried so hard for nothing.
They probably hope the witnesses are lying
so that they can continue investigating.
I know they are not lying.
How do you know?
Eyes are the window to your soul.
If you look to the left when you speak,
it means that you're recalling.
If you look to the right,
it means you're making things up.
When Jin Manlang and Mr. Du were speaking,
they were looking to the left.
What about the photo?
I burned it.
I first saw her
in the…
They did not have
the telltale sign of lying.
Smarty pants who like to lecture.
They did not lie,
but that doesn't mean
the two missing people
are not in danger.
Can you two stop arguing?
I analyzed everything in the box.
Nothing new.
Keep it or return it, it's your call.
I still have work to do.
THE GREEK COFFIN MYSTERY
MISSING PERSON
Why is this poster still here?
Isn't it weird?
Let me show you something weirder.
DEMOLITION
Does this look familiar to you?
Does this belong to Jin Manlang?
I returned everything back then.
This mooncake box belongs to Wolfie.
This detective novel belongs to Du Mandun.
Why are their things
kept together in the same place?
And look at the poster.
The paper and the ink are both new.
Weird, isn't it?
It has been so many years.
I never believed
that Yuanlongli was haunted.
YUXI CIGARETTE
Someone must be behind all of this.
407.
Du Mandun's unit.
He moved out several months ago.
So, it was all a false alarm.
Du Mandun moved out,
but he didn't take his books.
I remember he was quite invested
in the missing persons case back then.
He even discussed some conspiracies
or locked rooms with you.
Sir,
ever since we set foot into Yuanlongli,
you've been mentioning
that particular case.
What does it have to do
with the missing kid?
It has everything to do with it.
They are both missing person cases.
So?
So, we're looking for them.
Sir,
I came to Weiyang
to write the lesson plan,
and my schedule is tight enough.
Three floors left.
You gave me your word.
Now keep your promise.
Let's go.
WEIYANG PUBLIC SECURITY BUREAU
NANSHAN BRANCH
I already signed.
Please sign it, too.
CRIMINAL CASE REGISTRATION FORM
Since you always go to Qu Dahai,
ask him to sign it.
He doesn't have the power.
Neither do I.
Don't worry. After you sign it,
I'll be in charge of it.
You're a rookie. How
can you be in charge of it?
Our priority now is not to file a case.
It's to find those two people.
If you won't sign the registration form,
can you sign this?
EVIDENCE SUBPOENA REQUEST FORM
What is this?
The woman used medical patches.
I want to check the hospital records
to see if someone
injured their wrists lately.
You don't have
any real-life experience, do you?
Do you think
they will go to the hospital
for a small injury like this?
Where else could she
have gotten the patches?
In a pharmacy.
In a clinic.
Many people are selling
common medications.
Following your method, I can sign it,
and you still won't
find anything after years.
Then, how should we proceed?
Put up posters and wait on the bench?
Are you lecturing me right now?
At least I caught someone
after waiting the whole day.
What did you find?
Chicken blood?
Duck blood can be added to a hotpot.
But chicken blood? It's useless.
Enough.
-Will you sign it or not?
-No!
Criminal department.
Dad!
Yes. It's me.
You haven't come back in so long.
It's getting harder to see you now.
I'll come back soon.
Again?
Your soon is getting absurdly long.
Kiddo,
I recently ran into a troublemaker.
He keeps pestering me.
Then, buy me a bottle of Coke.
Don't tell Mom.
Sure.
Wait. Mom wants to talk to you.
Xiaohe.
Go back to your room.
He Yuanhang, where are you?
I'm working now.
I need to work hard to impress my boss.
That way, I can stay
in the criminal department.
Are you trying to get back
to the police station again?
Who says that? That's impossible.
I met Qu Dahai today.
He told me that.
-He said you'd return next week.
-Qu Dahai.
Listen. He's trying to break us up.
He can't wait to return
to the police station.
What? He Yuanhang!
It's noisy here.
The lines are mixed up.
-Officer He said only six days left till…
-Till I catch…
Wait. It's noisy here.
Only six days left till he goes back to…
Give me a moment.
Don't worry.
I'll work hard to stay
in the criminal department.
I have to hang up now.
I have a meeting soon. Okay.
Getting bolder now, huh?
Let's go.
You go ahead. I need to work.
Who says it's not about work?
We have a new lead.
Hey!
Wait for me.
Where are my shoes?
You have five minutes
to get yourself some new outfits
at the night market.
Sir, buy some leather shoes.
They are all genuine leather. Take a look.
We have a clearance sale today.
Everything is cheap. Trust me.
Sir, you have great taste.
Double Fish Heels. They are branded.
Are they for your girlfriend?
Sir.
Come. Take a look.
I also have stirrup pants. Get them too.
Blue and red, as beautiful as you get.
Sir, help me out, will you?
I'll forever remember your generosity.
Did you gain some common sense?
Boat orchids.
You splurged.
It's to compensate someone.
Compensate someone?
You're somehow attached
to these old sandals?
It's to compensate someone too.
It's to compensate someone too?
You have only worked for two days.
You didn't earn anything,
but you have to compensate
for losses already.
Well done.
Oh. Guess what I saw in the night market.
The blue leather heels
worn by the missing woman.
They are called Double Fish Heels.
A renowned brand, apparently.
Expensive too.
They come in different colors.
Red, black, and even white.
Why didn't you buy something
for your intelligence?
Branded goods in a night market?
How authentic can they be?
Hey. What are you doing?
Don't touch it.
If you break it, I'll be in trouble.
Is this your daughter's?
Yes.
How old is she?
Eight years old. Year 3.
Is she the reason why you don't want
to stay in the criminal department?
I know it wouldn't be because of you.
Stop asking questions.
It's none of your business.
You studied in Beijing.
But you are assigned to Weiyang.
Is your family okay with it?
You checked my file.
I didn't.
But when Captain Feng
gave me an apprentice,
I had to check what I'd be getting.
Let me reiterate.
-I am not your apprentice.
-All right.
Won't you get sick of nagging,
my dear apprentice?
I…
You look so pampered.
Your family must be rich.
What do your parents do?
SHANCHENG HOTPOT
He's quite handsome,
but his fashion sense is a bit lacking.
He is dressed like an old man.
I'll bring some drinks over.
What do you want?
Whatever you bring me.
I didn't know
it was your number on the poster.
If I had known it,
I wouldn't have called you.
I'm just helping out.
Their relatives are eager to find them.
Relatives?
Thanks, cutie.
You're… You're welcome.
MISSING PERSON
Do you know them?
The woman on the poster was my colleague.
Colleagues?
What's her name? What kind of work?
Ex-colleagues.
Her name is Mengmeng.
What kind of work?
A massage parlor.
No wonder she used medical patches.
What's her surname? Her full name, please.
Mengmeng is just a nickname.
Masseuses never use their real names.
Ignore him.
He's just a rookie who knows nothing.
Just share your information with me.
Cutie. Let me tell you the truth.
It's a massage parlor,
but we do all sorts of things there.
So, the girls there
are from other regions.
Mengmeng is the only local there.
I only know
that her father is quite sick.
She can't leave Weiyang.
Have you seen her father?
I guess it was the guy she was carrying.
Does Mengmeng have other relatives?
Didn't you tell me her relatives
were looking for her?
Police officers and citizens are a family.
I can't find her relatives,
but I'll help them find her first.
Officer He. The police can't find them.
Let alone a citizen like me.
Where is the parlor?
What is the name?
Ask him.
He raided the place.
Pattia.
Cutie. You've been there before?
How come I've never seen you?
No, not at all. I… I just came to Weiyang.
I just want to know if Mengmeng
is close to anyone else.
She is the quiet type.
Quite dull.
When she was not working,
she would make small talk with me.
A rich man often asked for her.
Sometimes, he would take her with him.
Rich man? What's his name?
Sun, I think.
I don't know his name.
Try to recall.
He asked for Mengmeng, not me.
Besides, who uses their real name
in this kind of place?
Do you know where Mengmeng went afterward?
She went to a foot massage parlor
in Tenglong Street.
I think it's called… Muse.
People in my line of work
are used to moving frequently.
Many went missing too,
but no one cares.
I don't care if others care about it,
but we will see it through.
Don't worry about it.
Allow me to thank you
on behalf of Mengmeng.
No need. It's our job.
Dig in. It's on me today.
What do you like to eat?
Anything.
Then, I'll add everything in.
SHANCHENG HOTPOT
Thank you for providing
crucial information.
We can help you claim the reward.
I don't want your money.
Remember. You owe me a meal of hotpot,
cutie.
Wait.
Is your father Su Qingyou?
This must be yours.
I've been looking for this photo.
Where did you find it?
Eighteenth floor of Yuanlongli.
Where Pattia was.
SU QINGYOU
Cutie,
when you're free,
you must visit the parlor.
I'll give you a nice surprise.
See you.
Are you here to investigate
the case or to flirt?
Go now.
Where to?
To find the surprise.
MUSE FOOT MASSAGE
-Sir!
-Dear sir!
-Come on in!
-We waited for so long.
You will go in through the main entrance.
I'll take the rear entrance.
If something happens, we'll surround them.
Wait.
When you're inside,
do you know what to say?
Say what? I'll speak
like I normally would.
I know.
Since you're so approachable,
why did you ask me to go in?
I'm worried they might recognize me.
Get that out of your mind!
Don't you know what I did?
Go now.
MUSE FOOT MASSAGE
Be patient. It's fine,
even if they are new.
There are some over there.
A few girls over there.
Hi, Mister.
First time here?
Yes.
Come in.
-Dear sir!
-Sir! Is it your first time here?
You want something?
Don't be shy.
Yes, don't be shy.
The price is over there.
Pick anything you like.
Anything will do.
Anything will do?
So which service then? Take a look.
You know what?
I want Mengmeng to massage me.
Mengmeng?
She is sick today.
She took sick leave.
Pick another one.
The girls here are very friendly.
Exactly.
Pick another one.
Where is your boss?
Behind.
I'll get her for you.
Okay.
Give me a second.
Raid!
Raid! Raid!
ROOM 3
Pervert! Pervert!
Pervert!
Stop!
You still won't stop?
Officer.
I just washed my feet. They are clean.
Ms. Zhao.
I spilled the feet water
on his face just now.
Is it funny?
Tell me.
When did all of you last see Mengmeng?
I don't know.
She stopped coming to work three days ago.
Why?
Did she run into trouble
on her last day here?
I don't know.
What could possibly happen here?
And how would I know
why she stopped coming to work?
Did she meet any clients
on her last day here?
I don't know.
No one picked her.
She didn't earn anything,
so she stopped coming.
You…
First, you said you didn't know.
Now, you said no one picked her.
So, do you know something or not?
Sir.
"I don't know" is my catchphrase.
Mengmeng and I are colleagues.
She's like my subordinate.
Why would she tell me about her troubles?
Ask them if you don't trust me.
Would you come to me
if you run into trouble?
See?
All right.
Surely, you must know
Mengmeng's real name.
Of course.
NRIC PHOTOCOPY
XU MENG
DAJIANCHANG NEIGHBORHOOD
Why didn't you tell the others
to raid the foot massage parlor?
You know nothing.
It's not the time to retrieve the net yet.
Let's wait till we find
Xu Meng and her father.
Stop searching.
It should be that unit.
DIE
A putrid stench.
Corpse?
Not sure.
It's locked from the inside.
I can't open it without the keys.
Don't just stand there.
Call for backup
and ask them to break the door.
Do you know how to do this?
We learned how to pick locks at school.
They sure taught you
many practical things.
Are you doing this on purpose?
Listen.
Once we get back, make sure we follow
the due process for breaking in.
FOR RENT
The meat is all rotten.
Look.
They didn't even put the food away.
Probably left in a hurry.
I only have one.
Poor thing.
Why did they break the wall?
Officer He.
Size 37.
DOUBLE FISH
Double Fish Heels.
Authenticity logo.
It's expensive to get the real ones.
Why did they break the wall?
To move the cupboard out?
So skinny.
No wonder Xu Meng
could carry her father on her back.
The father's teeth are quite unique.
PENICILLIN V TABLETS
That's odd.
What is?
I saw in the security footage
that her father was holding a cigarette.
It looks like a cigarette.
But he has a lung disease.
Why would he be smoking?
They have done weirder things.
Perhaps he thought it wasn't worth it.
Just smoke and drink however he wanted.
HOUSEHOLD REGISTER
HOUSEHOLD REGISTER, SAVINGS ACCOUNT
REGISTER OF PERMANENT RESIDENT, XU ZHIHONG
REGISTER OF PERMANENT RESIDENT, XU MENG
Bowls?
I've seen this brand in a mall in Beijing.
This dress is probably
more expensive than this flat.
It doesn't feel like something
Xu Meng would wear.
It doesn't match her style.
You sure know your fashion.
Police!